[rock guitar riff playing]
‎饼干拿来
[Leia, hoarsely] Cookie.
‎咱们能不能别刷《飞越比佛利》了？
Could we please stop the 90210 marathon?
‎我做了一个
‎关于安德里亚祖克曼的羞羞梦
I had a dirty dream
about Andrea Zuckerman.
‎感觉好懵
I'm so confused.
‎只有这部剧能陪我熬过
‎与杰伊分手的痛苦时光了
This show is the only thing
getting me through my breakup with Jay.
‎我知道你很难过
Oh, I know you're hurting.
‎但我再说一次
‎你得跟人家约会过才能分手哈
But, again, you actually have to date
someone to break up with them.
‎我还是更喜欢来地下室这边
[Leia scoffs] I like it better under here.
‎老天 怎么还在看《飞越比佛利》？
‎这也太没出息了
Oh my God. Still with the 90210?
This is getting pathetic.
‎这话我不会当面说
‎但这妹子得去看医生了
I'm not gonna say it to her face,
but she needs professional help.
‎昨天 我看到她在附近晃悠
I saw her yesterday wandering
just through the neighborhood
‎跟咱爷爷之前一样
like our grandpa used to.
‎没过几天他就走了
Near the end.
‎行了 别说了
Guys, stop.
‎她现在难受劲儿还没过呢
She's going through something.
‎还是为那种缺心眼儿的事
Something really stupid.
‎格温！我还在这儿呢
Gwen! I'm right here!
‎好得很 你得听人劝
Good. You needed to hear it.
[scoffs]
‎我还得难受多久啊？
How long am I going to feel this bad?
‎你要花恋爱的一半时长
‎才能走出分手阴影
It takes about half the time
you were in a relationship to get over it.
‎既然你没谈过恋爱…
And since you were never
in a relationship…
‎你没事了
You're good.
[Leia scoffs]
‎拜托 莉亚 别再钻你的伤心洞了
Leia, come on.
Don't go back into your sad hole.
‎我们是来送你生日礼物的
We came by to give you
your birthday present.
[chill psychedelic music playing]
‎伙计们 这礼物我喜欢
‎你们怎么知道我的尺码的？
Guys, I love it. How did you know my size?
‎我们给你买了超大号
‎好让大家一起享用
We got you an extra large
so we can enjoy it too.
‎这椅子是不是太小了？
Is this chair too small?
‎赶紧把生日卡给莉亚啊
Just give Leia our birthday card already.
‎里猫猫
Inside cat.
‎外猫猫
[gasps] Outside cat.
‎里猫猫 外猫猫 里…
Inside cat. Outside cat. Ins--
‎别猫猫了
No more cat.
‎我好想你们
‎没有你们 我的伤心洞好寂寞
I missed you guys.
My sad hole was lonely without you.
‎我不会让分手毁了我的生日
I'm not gonna let my breakup with Jay
ruin my birthday.
‎这不叫分手
Not a breakup.
‎-不叫分手
‎-不叫分手？
[both] Not a breakup.
‎人生中能有几回十五岁？
How many times
do you turn 15 in your life?
‎没几回
Not that many.
‎我看开了
I'm over him.
‎新的一年 新的我
New year, new me.
‎新街边男孩
New Kids On The Block.
‎我调得太低了
I over-corrected.
‎怎么回事？你把我的名字拼错了
What's this?
You spelled my name wrong on this card.
‎你怎么连女友的名字都不会拼？
How do you not know
how to spell your girlfriend's name?
‎让我看看
Let me see that.
-[Nikki scoffs]
-[chuckles]
‎妮可
Nik!
‎要走了吗？我才刚调好
People are leaving? I just got this right.
‎一 二 三 四
-[rock music playing]
-One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎（90年代秀）
‎你好 威斯康辛！
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎哎 唐娜和艾瑞克没法帮莉亚庆生了
Well, Donna and Eric aren't gonna make it
for Leia's birthday.
‎艾瑞克很郁闷
‎可他又不是不知道参加太空营有风险
Eric's upset, but he knew the risks
when he signed up for Space Camp.
‎凯蒂 他从铺上摔下来了
‎又不是上了阿波罗13号
Kitty, he fell out of his bunk bed.
It's not exactly Apollo 13.
‎那他可要后悔没睡下铺了
Well, he is gonna wish
he slept on the bottom bunk
‎因为我要开一场
‎凯蒂福尔曼经典生日狂欢
because I am throwing
a classic Kitty Forman birthday bash.
‎老伙计 咱俩又要联手了
It's you and me, old friend.
‎我们要奉上一台好戏
We're about to put on a show.
‎你在策划一场儿童派对
You're planning a kid's party.
‎所以这次尽量别那么大压力
So let's try and not
get all stressed out this time.
‎别担心
Don't worry.
‎我特意早起做准备
I woke up early to get a head start.
‎老天爷 都七点了 我还啥都没弄呢！
Oh my God, it's 7:00 a.m.
I haven't deviled a damn thing!
‎我那份已经准备好了
Well, I did my part.
‎礼物搞定
Took care of the gift.
‎20美元
Twenty dollars.
‎你就做一件事 爽死你了
-You did one thing. Good for you.
-[egg cracks]
‎抱歉 我发脾气了 就…过生日真好玩
I'm sorry. I snapped.
It's… Birthdays are fun.
[laughs]
‎今天会很漫长
It's gonna be a long day.
‎哈啰 哈啰 哈啰啰
Hey there! Hi there! Ho there!
‎这下更漫长了
And it just got longer.
‎鲍勃 你来啦
-Bob. You made it.
-[Bob laughs]
[Kitty coos]
‎你知道他要来？
You knew about this?
‎你不知道 所以他才来得成
And you didn't, and that's why he's here.
‎-嗨！
‎-嗨
-Hi!
-[Bob] Hi.
‎我给你带了新鲜的佛罗里达橙
I brought you some fresh Florida oranges.
‎我在飞机上拿它当枕头来着
I used them as a pillow on the plane.
‎里面要是有卷毛儿 那都是我的
So, if you find any curly hairs in there,
that's me.
‎那我把这些放进洗碗机
Well, I am just gonna put these
in the dishwasher.
[both laugh]
‎小寿星来啦
There's the birthday girl!
‎生日快乐
Happy birthday.
‎我先说的
I said it first.
‎嘿 鲍勃姥爷
Hey, Grandpa Bob.
‎瞅瞅
Ooh! Look at you.
‎你可真漂亮
You are so darn beautiful.
‎潘西亚蒂家的基因依然很牛
Those Pinciotti genes
are strong like a bull.
‎牛啥就不一定了
Bull-something.
‎牛奶是开派对用的！
That milk's for the party!
‎我是说 生日快乐 亲爱的
I mean, happy birthday, honey.
‎孩儿啊 生日快乐
Happy birthday, kiddo.
‎奶奶没事吧？
Is Grandma all right?
‎最好别惹她
I'd lay low.
[rock music playing]
‎如果你连我的名字都不会拼
If you don't even know
how I spell my name,
‎那关于我还有什么是你不知道的？
what else do you not know about me?
‎妮可 我也不知道我不知道啥
I don't know what I don't know, Nik.
‎问问我关于你咪咪的事儿
‎我可以画在餐巾纸上
Ask me something about your boobs.
I can draw those on a napkin.
‎你过生日 还请我们吃饭？
You're buying us lunch on your birthday?
‎我觉得应该感谢你们
‎这个礼拜这么照顾我
I felt like I needed to thank you guys
for taking care of me this week.
‎我也没有太惨 是吧？
I wasn't too bad, was I?
[laughs heartily, inhales sharply]
‎哦 你没开玩笑啊
Oh, you weren't kidding.
‎太好了 你终于意识到
‎在男人身上浪费这么多时间有多傻了
I'm glad you finally realized it's dumb
to let a man waste so much of your time.
‎那是我们该做的
That's our job.
‎你说得对 我要过一个精彩的生日
You're right.
I'm going to have a great birthday.
‎再也不会闷闷不乐了
All that moping around stuff
is in the past.
‎很好
Good.
‎因为杰伊和赛琳娜刚刚进来了
'Cause Jay and Serena just walked in.
‎糟了 她又要丧了
This is bad. She's gonna have a relapse.
‎就是 莉亚 这场面对你没好处 走吧
Yeah. Leia, you don't need this right now.
Let's just get outta here.
‎说真的 伙计们 我没事的
Seriously, guys, I'm fine.
‎我现在就过去
‎像普通人一样打个招呼
I'm gonna go over there
and say hi like a normal person.
‎你们这些笨蛋怎么样啊？
How's it going, turkeys?
‎我喜欢她的肢体语言 坚强 自信
I like her body language.
Strong, assertive.
‎她刚刚拿起一条腌黄瓜
She just picked up a pickle.
‎今天是我生日
So today's my birthday. [chuckles]
‎新的一年 全新开始 十五岁可是大年
New year, startin' fresh.
The big one-five.
‎好可爱啊
‎我都不怎么记得十五岁生日了
Aww, that's so cute!
I barely even remember turning 15.
‎当时好像是在巴哈马
I think I was in the Bahamas.
‎我也是
Me too!
‎可你现在在这里啊
But you're here right now.
‎不 在这里的是你
No, you're here.
‎反正呢 今晚开派对
Anywhistle, big party tonight.
‎我奶奶请了桥牌俱乐部的牌友
‎所以肯定是要掀房盖儿了
My grandma's inviting her bridge club,
so the roof shall be raised.
[chuckles]
‎哎呀 我真没礼貌 你们也来玩吧
Actually, I'm so rude.
You guys should come.
‎-你确定吗？
‎-当然了
-Are you sure?
-Of course.
‎我希望所有的朋友和他们新女友都来
I want all my friends
and their new girlfriends at my party.
‎那太好了 我们去
Okay, great. We'll be there.
‎我也是 都等不及了
As will I. Cannot wait.
‎我毁了自己的生日
[sighs] I just ruined my birthday.
‎这时候你们该告诉我
‎我没有毁掉自己的生日
This is where you're supposed to tell me
I didn't just ruin my birthday.
‎但你有
But you did.
‎这根腌黄瓜真是灾星！
This pickle's bad luck!
‎把你的恶魔咸菜拿远点
Don't put your demon pickle near me.
‎你那只手不想要了？
You wanna lose that hand?
‎很少有人能夺走纸杯蛋糕的欢乐
You know, it's hard
to take the joy out of a cupcake.
‎你居然做到了
But you did.
‎你要是不想给我帮忙
‎那就去客厅坐着
Well, if you don't wanna help me,
you can go sit in the living room
‎跟鲍勃聊他的假睾丸
and talk to Bob
about his prosthetic testicle.
‎你干嘛非请他来？
Why did you have to invite him?
‎我真不懂 你干嘛这么不爽
‎毕竟他是莉亚的外公
I don't know what you're getting
worked up about. He's Leia's grandpa too.
‎都怪艾瑞克
I blame Eric.
‎管鲍勃叫爹的姑娘就那么一个
There's only one girl in the world
with Bob as her dad,
‎而他偏偏要选她
and he had to pick her.
‎我说 今天有啥菜啊？
Hey there, what's cookin'?
‎在厨房问这个正合适
-'Cause we're in the kitchen.
-Oh.
‎该死
Damn it.
‎念叨三回就把他招来了
‎就跟《阴间大法师》似的
We said his name three times
and summoned him like Beetlejuice.
‎我来做个拿手的蛤蜊蘸酱
‎为派对助兴
I'm gonna make my famous clam dip
for the party.
‎真贴心 但我们已经准备很多吃的了
Oh, that's sweet,
but we have plenty of food for tonight.
‎我知道 但孩子们肯定想吃点好吃的
I know, but the kids are gonna want
something good.
‎我在那儿化火腿呢
I was thawing a ham in there.
‎我只是太激动了
I'm just excited.
‎莉亚今年过生日 我可是下血本了
You know, I went all out
on Leia's birthday gift this year.
‎我给她买了一台卡拉OK唱机
I got her a karaoke machine.
‎-那东西不是很贵吗？
‎-就是啊
-Aren't those things expensive?
-Oh yeah. [chuckles]
‎我没撕价签
I left the price tag on.
‎我希望她…能记住我有多爱他
'Cause I want her to…
[voice breaking]
…remember how much I love her.
‎我得静一静
[weeping] I need a minute!
‎这小子以为他能砸我的场子？
This guy thinks he can run my party?
‎拿蛤蜊斗火腿？休想
Clam my ham? No, sir!
‎你的火腿好歹还能洗洗干净 凯蒂
You can rinse off your ham, Kitty.
‎我那20块钱刚刚被卡拉OK唱机碾压了
My 20 bucks is getting its ass kicked
by a karaoke machine.
‎那就拿出点气势 雷德
Well, then, step it up, Red.
‎你蛋蛋比他多一倍 那就有点种
You've got twice the balls, act like it.
[rock music playing]
‎伙计们 我好像想明白
You guys, I think I figured out
‎为什么会请杰伊和他女友来派对了
why I invited Jay and his girlfriend
to my party.
‎你准备好了吗？
You ready?
‎我还在留恋杰伊
I'm not over Jay.
‎-我的天 不会吧
‎-啥？
-Oh my God. No way.
-What?
‎就是说啊
[chuckles] I know!
‎我也很惊讶
I'm surprised too.
‎这都是我的错
And it's all my fault.
‎因为…我根本就是布兰达
Because, guys…
-I'm Brenda.
-Brenda?
‎-布兰达？
‎-《飞越比佛利》里的布兰达
-Brenda Walsh, from 90210.
-[Ozzie sighs]
‎布兰达对那个男人很执着
‎但她从来不去追那个男人
Brenda obsesses over the guy,
but she never goes for the guy.
[pop rock theme music playing]
[percussion plays]
‎（飞越点域镇）
‎（莉亚）
‎（格温）
‎（杰伊）
‎（奥兹）
‎（内特）
‎（妮基）
‎（雷德）
‎（凯蒂）
‎（布莱恩奥斯丁饰大卫）
[class bell ringing]
‎人们总是说我在逃跑
All my life, people told me
I was running away.
‎但其实
But, really,
‎我一直在奔向一个人
I've been running to something.
‎是我 对吧？
It's me, isn't it?
‎是的
It is.
‎嘿 莉亚 今晚我要给派对做DJ
‎你想来吗？肯定超赞的
Hey, Leia. I'm DJing a party tonight.
You wanna come? It's gonna be fresh.
‎现在不行 大卫
Not now, David.
‎就因为我高一 是吗？
It's because I'm a freshman, isn't it?
[pop rock theme music plays]
‎也就是说
‎布兰达是一个被动戏多的受气包
So Brenda's the passive,
overly dramatic doormat.
‎这就说得通了
This makes sense now.
‎就是说吧？
[gasps and laughs] I know, right?
‎但你知道谁总能把帅哥追到手吗？
But you know who always gets the guy?
‎娇贵人气金发女凯莉
Kelly, the popular blonde
with the rich-girl attitude.
[pop rock theme music playing]
[percussion plays]
‎（飞越点域镇）
[upbeat rock music playing]
‎人们总是说我在逃跑
All my life, people told me
I was running away.
‎但其实
But, really,
‎我一直在奔向一个人
I've been running to something.
‎是我 对吧？
It's me, isn't it?
‎才怪 贱人 是我
No, bitch. It's me.
‎-莉亚？
‎-是凯莉
-Leia?
-It's Kelly.
‎伙计们 今晚我要给派对做DJ
‎你们想来吗？肯定超赞的
Hey, guys. I'm DJing a party tonight.
You wanna come? It's gonna be fresh.
‎现在不行 大卫
Not now, David.
‎就因为我高一 是吗？
It's because I'm a freshman, isn't it?
[pop rock theme plays, fades out]
‎我喜欢 介意我发挥一下下吗？
I like it.
Mind if I riff on it a little bit?
[pop rock theme music playing]
[percussion plays]
‎（飞越点域镇）
‎伙计们 今晚我要给派对做DJ
‎肯定超赞的
Hey, guys. I'm DJing a party.
It's gonna be fresh.
‎有个超赞的霹雳舞者会来 瞅瞅
This totally rad breakdancer's
gonna be there. Check it.
‎音乐走起
Drop that beat.
[old school hip-hop beat playing]
[students exclaiming]
‎我从没见过这么酷的娃
That's the coolest kid I've ever seen!
[pop rock theme music plays, fades out]
‎不会吧 哥们儿？
Really, dude?
‎大卫从不骗人
David don't lie.
‎等杰伊和赛琳娜来参加派对
‎我就用凯莉的方式
When Jay and Serena show up at my party,
I'm gonna show 'em what's what.
‎让他们搞搞清楚状况
Kelly-style.
‎难怪我们跟男人同工不同酬
This is why we get paid 30% less than men.
‎你不是对杰伊没执念了吗？
What happened to not obsessing over Jay?
‎我没有执念
I'm not obsessing.
‎我只是改变外表、行为和想法
‎让他回心转意
I'm just gonna change how I look
and how I act and how I think
‎我只是改变外表、行为和想法
‎让他回心转意
to win him back.
‎-喂！你这是干嘛？
‎-让你振作起来
-Hey! What was that for?
-To snap you out of it.
‎干嘛呀！
Dude!
‎嘿！
Hey!
‎好了 住手
Ow. Stop.
‎我是对这种剧情不感兴趣
I am the wrong audience for this.
‎别闹了！
[Leia] Ow!
‎我准备好礼物了
-I got the gift.
-[Kitty gasps]
‎鲍勃去哪儿了？
-Where's Bob?
-Oh.
‎他嘛…
Well…
‎他搞得我抓狂 于是…
He was driving me crazy, so I…
‎我把感冒药掺在他的冰茶里了
I put some cold medicine in his iced tea.
‎还有他的土豆沙拉里
And some in his potato salad.
‎还有他的布丁里
Some more in his pudding.
‎雷德 他…就是不肯消停
‎感觉就像…给犀牛下药
He just… He wouldn't go down, Red.
It was like… drugging a rhino.
‎反正哩 他在楼上睡得正香
Anyhoo, he's fast asleep upstairs.
‎你就等着看我给莉亚准备的礼物吧
Wait till you see what I got Leia.
‎鲍勃砸钱 我用心
Bob went expensive, but I went thoughtful.
‎你可真是贴心呢
You sweet, sweet man.
‎她专属的无绳电钻
Her own cordless drill.
‎你可真是笨呢
You stupid, stupid man.
‎多好的礼物啊 帮她自立
But it's a great gift.
It gives her independence.
‎她可以自己修东西 自己照顾自己
She can fix things on her own.
Take care of herself.
‎你干嘛那样看着我？
Why are you looking at me like that?
‎莫非我没说这是无绳的？
Did I not say it was cordless?
‎雷德 你得用青少年的思维思考
Red, you need to think like a teenager.
‎你十五岁时想要什么？
What did you want when you were 15?
‎小儿麻痹症疫苗
A vaccine for polio.
‎好吧 我继续找
All right. I'll keep looking.
‎乖乖…我肯定是累坏了
Man… I must have been really tired.
‎我在厅里睡着了
I fell asleep in the hallway.
‎嗯…倒时差可辛苦了
Well… you know,
that jet lag can be a killer.
‎我再给你拿点冰茶
Let me get you some more iced tea.
[rock music playing]
[Kitty] Ooh!
‎某人胃口不错呢
Somebody brought their appetite.
‎你最喜欢我哪道开胃菜？
So which one of my hors d'oeuvres
do you like best?
‎这个蛤蜊蘸酱…我超爱
This clam dip? Love!
‎哎呀呀
Whoopsie.
‎好了 我习惯高跟鞋了 你可以放手了
Okay, I've figured out high heels.
You can let go now.
‎你要站在这里等杰伊吗？
So you're gonna stand here
and wait for Jay?
‎对呀 等他来了
‎我要像凯莉一样把他的脸啃烂
Yeah. And when he gets here,
I'm gonna grab him and Kelly his face off.
‎（一小时后）
[dramatic rock guitar riff plays]
‎太丢脸了
This is so embarrassing.
‎我以为我能让杰伊回心转意
‎但他根本不在乎 来都没有来
I thought I could win back Jay,
but he didn't even care enough to show.
‎我懂
I get it.
‎没人来“核桃咖啡馆”看我当DJ
No one came to watch me
DJ at the Peach Pit.
‎连唐娜马丁都没来
Not even Donna Martin.
‎太糟糕了
It's the worst.
‎她在场下人怎么样？
What was she like? I mean, between scenes?
‎什么叫“场”？
What do you mean, "scenes"?
‎算了
Never mind.
‎谢谢你来参加我的生日派对 大卫
Thank you for coming
to my birthday, David.
‎-我最喜欢你了
‎-这个我爱听
-You were always my favorite.
-I'll take it.
‎你在跟谁说话？
Who are you talking to?
‎大卫 没谁
Uh, David. Nobody.
‎这样太傻了
This is stupid.
‎因为惦记杰伊 我整个生日都浪费了
I wasted my whole birthday
thinking about Jay,
‎而他显然已经向前看了
and he's clearly moved on.
‎我才不要继续可怜下去
I'm done being pathetic.
‎终于开窍了
Finally!
‎让开 他来了！
-[doorbell chimes]
-Move, he's here! Move, he's here!
‎鲍勃姥爷？
Grandpa Bob?
‎你是说汤姆琼斯姥爷
You mean Grandpa Tom Jones.
‎我来用你的生日礼物给你唱生日歌
I'm here to sing your birthday song
on your birthday gift.
‎你唱歌？当着我朋友？穿那件衣服？
You're gonna sing?
In front of my friends? In that jacket?
‎我要站那边去了
I'll be over here.
‎汤姆琼斯？
Tom Jones?
‎更像是汤姆从沙发起身穷哼唧
‎你说是不是？
More like Tom groans
getting up from the couch. Am I right?
‎就是
I am right.
[soft karaoke instrumental playing]
‎歌放错了 但演出还要继续
Wrong song, but, hey, the show must go on.
‎我想把这首歌
‎献给我美丽的外孙女莉亚
I'd like to dedicate this song
to my beautiful granddaughter, Leia.
‎这首歌唱给你听
This one's for you.
‎坏了
Oh no.
♪ Close your eyes ♪
♪ Make a wish ♪
♪ And blow out the candlelight ♪
‎能行呢 这是首生日歌
Hey, it worked out. It's a birthday song.
‎这首不是生日歌
This is not a birthday song.
‎我们一起挺过去
We'll ride it out together.
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ Like you want me to ♪
♪ And I'll hold you tight ♪
♪ Baby, all through the night… ♪
‎这是我们的歌
This is our song. [chuckles]
[Bob continues singing]
‎你第一次让我摸你屁股时
‎电台就在放这首歌
It was playing on the radio the first time
you let me touch your butt.
‎你还记得
Oh, you remembered!
♪ And I will not let go
Till you tell me to ♪
‎想出去透透气吗？
Wanna get some air?
‎必须的
Oh God, yes.
♪ Girl, relax ♪
‎鲍勃 没人放松的了
Bob. Nobody's relaxed.
‎孩儿啊 你今天晚上好像不太好过啊
Seems like you might have had
a rough night, kiddo.
‎今天是我十五岁的第一天
‎可我一点也不开心
I've only been 15 for a day,
and so far I don't like it.
‎没有一件事顺心
I mean, nothing's gone right.
‎感觉我都不知道自己在做什么
It's like I don't know what I'm doing.
‎怎么说呢
Well,
‎事事不可能总会顺心
everything's not gonna go right.
‎别这么为难自己
‎毕竟你有一半笨蛋血统
Give yourself a break.
You're half dumbass.
‎只是…
It's just…
‎其他人好像都活得明明白白
‎而我只能随机应变
Everyone else seems to have it all
figured out and I'm just making it all up.
‎娃啊 那我有坏消息要告诉你
Well, I hate to break it to you, kid,
‎大家都是一路随机应变
but we're all just making it up
as we go along.
‎所以 别太为难自己
So don't be so hard on yourself.
‎谢谢你 爷爷
Thanks, Grandpa.
‎嘿 等等
Oh. Hey, wait.
‎你不想要你的礼物吗？
Don't you want your present?
["Slow Ride" opening riff playing]
♪ Slow ride… ♪
‎车？你给我买了辆车？
A car? You got me a car?
‎它原来是你爸爸的
It belonged to your father.
‎明天我们帮你申请学员执照
‎我会教你怎么开车 好吧？
Tomorrow, we'll get your learner's permit,
and I'll teach you how to drive. Okay?
‎谢谢你 爷爷
Thank you, Grandpa.
‎这是我收到过最棒的礼物
This is the best present I've ever gotten.
Oh…
‎记得把这话告诉你鲍勃姥爷
Be sure to say that to Grandpa Bob.
‎孩儿啊 生日快乐
Happy birthday, kiddo.
-♪ Slow ridin' woman, you're so fine ♪
-[song fades out]
‎你把那辆“远景巡洋舰”送她了？
You gave her the Vista Cruiser?
‎乖乖 你净掐我命根子
Man, you really creamed my jeans.
‎你认输都不能正常点儿？
Can't you even lose like a normal person?
‎好了 雷德 这又不是比赛
Now, Red, it wasn't a competition.
‎我想为莉亚尽一份心
I wanted to do something nice for Leia.
‎你们真有福分 能跟她长久相处
You guys are lucky
to spend all this time with her.
‎我只希望她别忘了自己的鲍勃姥爷
I don't want her
to forget about her ol' Grandpa Bob.
Oh.
‎该死
Damn it.
‎鲍勃 你是个好人
You're a good man, Bob.
‎烦得要死 但是个好人
Annoying as hell, but a good man.
‎身边有你 是莉亚的福分
Leia is lucky to have you.
‎你们都把我整哭了
You guys are makin' me emotional.
‎我从来不哭的
And I never cry.
‎鲍勃 这里随时欢迎你来
Bob, you are welcome here anytime.
[chuckles]
Ooh.
‎我得去方便方便
I gotta see a man about a clam. [chuckles]
‎“随时”？
"Anytime"?
‎雷德 大家都是一家人
Red, he's family.
‎艾瑞克！
[grumbles] Eric!
[rapping on window]
‎杰伊？
Jay?
‎喂 介意我进来吗？
Hey. Mind if I come in?
‎好吧 但派对结束了
Okay, but the party's over.
‎我知道 抱歉我错过了
[strains] Yeah. I'm sorry I missed it.
‎我只是觉得和赛琳娜一起来不太好
It just didn't feel right
to show up with Serena.
‎我还是不明白 我干嘛要邀请她
I still don't know why I invited her.
‎-我只是希望你能来
‎-我也想来
-I just wanted you to be there.
-I wanted to be there too.
‎不过…至少我可以祝你生日快乐
But… at least I can wish you
a happy birthday.
‎知道吗？不然就来不及了
You know? Before it's too late.
‎你这是怎么了？
Whoa. Where did that come from?
‎大概是我随机应变吧
I guess I'm just
making it up as I go along.
‎-你得跟赛琳娜分手
‎-赛琳娜是谁？
-You need to break up with Serena.
-Serena who?
[Jay chuckles]
["The World I Know"
by Collective Soul playing]
‎你想去开车兜风吗？
Hey, you wanna go for a drive?
‎-想啊 但我没有车
‎-这不成问题
Yeah, but I don't have a car.
‎-想啊 但我没有车
‎-这不成问题
[laughs softly] Not a problem.
♪ So I walk up on high… ♪
‎-嘿 我们接吻了
‎-我知道
-Hey, we kissed.
-I know.
‎今年生日最棒了
This is the best birthday.
[siren wails]
‎酷一点
Just be cool.
‎可我这辈子没酷过 怎么办？
You mean, for the first time in my life?!
♪ While the tears roll down ♪
♪ 'Cause it's the world I know ♪
♪ Oh, it's the world I know ♪
[rock music playing]
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu